indexification.com 2017-07-03

# INDEXIFICATION - Privacy Policy

We highly respect Your privacy! Please, take a read on this page to learn about Our privacy policy. 

### Our Privacy Policy Coverage

This policy covers how "We" treat any kind of personal information collected and received from Our clients, user and visitors of this website and any other online business owned by "Indexification". This includes personal information related to your current or past use of "Indexification" services, products or website visits.

**This Privacy Policy applies ONLY to practices of "Indexification" and DOES NOT apply to practices "Indexification" has no control over, or to people and/or companies who are not part of "Indexification" company!**

### Personal Information Definition

Personal information described by "Indexification" is any of the following: name, address, country, email address, phone number, instant messengers account names, IP Address and any other private information about Your personality that isn't publicly available. 

### Personal Information Collection and Use

"Indexification" collects and receives personal information for couple of reasons. The first and most important reason is to provide you convenient access and use of our services and products. Second reason is for internal "Indexification" company statistics about the use of products and services. Third reason is to keep you notified on important news regarding your use or our products or services.

"Indexification" may combine the personal information we receive across all our online business sites, services and products. 

### How Personal Information is being collected?

Personal Information at "Indexification" is being collected in various ways. We receive information about you, whenever you subcribe or purchase our service or product. We receive information about you, if you subscribe to our newsletter or you use our "recommend to friend" online form. We deploy tracking capabilities on all our sites, services and products for internal company statistics of the use of our sites, services or products. All this collected data is stored in a secure location at our servers, so that only "Indexification" has access and control over it! 

### Personal Information Sharing and Disclosure

"Indexification" does not sell,share,trade,rent or take outside the company information about you to third parties except to provide you services or products you have requested or under any of the following circumstances: 

  * We are required by the law or legal processes to disclosure your information.
  * We find it necessary to share information about you with the legal institutions in case you violated any of our terms of services and policies.
  * We find it necessary to share information about you to investigate/prevent illegal activities.
  * We may transfer information about you in case our company is merged with another one. In this case you will be notified, before information about you is transferred and new privacy policy will be applied.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review this page regularly for any changes. "Indexification" will notify or place prominent notice on our websites, services or products in case of any significant changes to this Privacy Policy!
